{"title": "Chapter 173: Second approval (4)", "text": "He wanted to leave a good impression for the first time, but with the person refusing to meet with him, it seemed it was better to go this way than to charge in through the mansion. The mansion was small, so the distance was enough.\n\nôI will have to excuse you.ö\n\nôYes?ö\n\nChun Yeowun then brought up powerful energy and exploded out toward the mansion. YeowunÆs energy at the supreme level was enough to provoke equal level warrior.\n\nôM-master?!ö\n\nKo Wanghur, Mun Ku and even Hu Bong were shocked by the power. Ones with weaker internal energy felt their legs shaking from powerful energy pressing down on them.\n\nôNnnnnahhhh!ö\n\nThe man, who was just an ordinary man, became pale and slumped down to the ground. With such powerful energy focused on the mansion, it was sure that Yin Moha will react in some way if she is interested as a martial artist.\n\næHuh?Æ\n\nBut there was no reaction from inside. Yeowun became dumbfounded.\n\næIs it as Left Guardian said?Æ\n\nHe didnÆt think she would be this much uninterested in outside affairs. He had to at least meet her to see if he can persuade, but this was no use. Yeowun thought for a while and decided to check on something before he left.\n\næLeft Guardian said she has some ties to the Wise and Sword clan.Æ\n\nIf she is their supporter, then Yeowun needed to strike her down sooner then later. If Yin Moha, powerful martial artist equaling to those of elders from six clans support them, then it only meant YeowunÆs forces will be in trouble.\n\nôCan you send my message to the 10th elder then?ö\n\nôY-yes! Of course!ö\n\nThe staff answered quickly with a frightened voice.\n\nôTell her I asked æDo you walk the same path with Wise and Sword clan?'ö\n\nHe decided to ask directly. If she is truly their supporter, she will react and if not, she will not show any response.\n\nôW-wait a second.ö\n\nThe man grabbed his shaking leg and walked back into the mansion. Ko Wanghur then asked Chun Yeowun with a curious look.\n\nôMaster, are you not here to receive approval from the 10th elder? Why do you ask such a thing?ö\n\nIt was natural as only Yeowun was the one who heard about the connection of the 10th elder with Sword and Wise clan. Yeowun then answered to Wanghur.\n\nôIÆm checking to see if sheÆll remain as an observer, or become an enemy.ö\n\nôàSo, youÆve given up on her medal.ö\n\nIf she was this stubborn, then it seemed impossible to persuade her to join them anyway. The best scenario then was to have her remain as neutral in the fight between six clans. And it was not long after the staff went back into the mansion.\n\nYeowun turned to the inside of the mansion. Sharp energy began to rumble from inside, and Yeowun became grim.\n\næSo, sheÆs the latter.Æ\n\nFrom the energy, it was sure that she wasnÆt going to be an observer.\n\nôW-what is with this energy!?ö\n\nôAh-ah!ö\n\nKo Wanghur and Mun Ku also felt the energy bit after Yeowun, and became shocked. This was as powerful as the energy that unleashed from Chun Yeowun just a moment ago. It was certain that this energy was coming from the owner of this mansion. ThatÆs when the staff ran out in a pale face and spoke to Yeowun and his members.\n\nôM-master wants you to come in.ö\n\n10th Elder Yin Moha invited them in. Yeowun nodded and walked into the mansion. As he walked over the gate, there was a large yard that was filled with sand and the building that Yin Moha lived.\n\næOh! SheÆs the 10th elder!Æ\n\nMun Ku looked at the mansion intriguingly. On the inside of the building, at the terrace, there was a woman looking to be in her 50s, with white clothes. She stood tall and proud, and thick eyebrows and wrinkles over her forehead that showed that she was not an ordinary woman.\n\næSword?Æ\n\nAnd on her right hand, there was a sword. It seemed she didnÆt invite for hospitality. Yin Moha got down from the terrace and before Yeowun can bow, she pointed at his face and spoke.\n\nôSo, itÆs you.ö\n\nô??ö\n\nKo Wanghur and Hu Bong became angry at such rude gesture. Even if both of them were the same elders, Chun Yeowun was the son of the Lord and candidate of the heir. At least basic manners were required, but she was pointing at Yeowun and acting rudely.\n\næSo, she sure is strange.Æ\n\nShe looked like a noble woman at first, but she was very rough. It was possible to see why even the Lord considered her difficult. Even to her attitude, Yeowun did not mind it and bowed.\n\nô12th Elder, Chun Yeowun here to meet 10th Elder, Yin Moha.ö\n\nôBah! I donÆt care if you are from Chun, or the elder. I pay no respect to anyone other than the Lord of the Cult.ö\n\nIt was merely an introduction, but she was hostile. Yeowun became grim.\n\næSo, sheÆs with the Wise and Sword clan.Æ\n\nIf that wasnÆt the case, there was no reason for her to react in such a way. ThatÆs when Yin Moha suddenly pulled out her sword.\n\næW-what?!Æ\n\næWhat is she doing?!Æ\n\nYeowunÆs members became grim at Yin MohaÆs sudden movement. The sword revealed its dark cold steel blade, and she charged against Yeowun with a hostile look and shouted.\n\nôYou said what? Same path!? You dare consider me as those despicable betrayers?! I will teach you a lesson!!!ö\n\nAnd with that, Yin Moha charged like a lightning and unleashed powerful sword movement at Yeowun. Mun Ku shouted with shock.\n\nôPrince! Watch OUT!ö\n\nAnd in that short moment, Chun YeowunÆs eye grew large. This powerful sword formation, that increased its power by having 18 sword movement combining itself, was the formation that Yeowun very well knew.\n\næTrue Demon Sword?Æ\n\nThis was the True Demon Sword, the sword skill created by Sword Demon, that 10th Elder Yin Moha was using."}
